{
  "type": "fill_in_the_blank_list",
  "title": "Fill in the Blank (.5 points each)",
  "instructions": "Type the correct answer(s) in the blank(s).",
  "points_per_question": 0.5,
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "What are Bartle's Player Types? \n___ \n___ \n___ \n___",
      "answers": [["killers"], ["achievers"], ["explorers"], ["socializers"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List four of Quantic Foundry's Gamer Types: ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["acrobat"],["gardener"],["slayer"],["skirmisher"],["gladiator"],["ninja"],["bounty hunter"],["architect"],["bard"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List six of Quantic Foundry's twelve Gamer motivations: ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["destruction"],["excitement"],["competition"],["community"],["challenge"],["strategy"],["completion"],["power"],["fantasy"],["story"],["design"],["discovery"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List three of Quantic Foundry's six gaming motivation clusters: ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["action"], ["mastery"], ["social"], ["creativity"], ["immersion"], ["achievement"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What are the three parts of the MDA framework? \n___ \n___ \n___",
      "answers": [["mechanics"], ["dynamics"], ["aesthetics"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List 5 major genres of video games (super-genres, not sub-genres): \n___ \n___ \n___ \n___ \n___",
      "answers": [["action"], ["adventure"], ["role-playing"], ["simulation"], ["sports"], ["strategy"], ["puzzle"], ["idle"],["racing"], ["simulation"],["fighting"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name four of the eight types of fun: ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["sensation"], ["fantasy"], ["narrative"], ["challenge"], ["fellowship"], ["discovery"], ["expression"], ["submission"]] 
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name the major 9th generation consoles: ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["playStation 5"], ["xbox series x/s"], ["nintendo switch"], ["ps5"], ["xbox"], ["switch"], ["nintendo switch 2"], ["switch 2"], ["switch2"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name the four types of interface (input) modalities for games ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["inertial"], ["touch"],["audio"], ["video"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What are the fundamental attributes of games according to Chris Crawford? \n___ \n___ \n___ \n___",
      "answers": [["representation"], ["interaction"], ["conflict"], ["safety"]]
    }

  ]
}